[
  {
    "question": "Why don't elephants ride tricycles?",
    "answer": "They don't have thumbs to ring the bell"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why do elephants wear little green hats?",
    "answer": "So they can sneak across pool tables without being seen"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you know an elephant is in bed with you?",
    "answer": "He's the one with a big E on his pajamas"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you know an elephant has been in the refrigerator?",
    "answer": "You can see the footprints in the butter"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why do elephants paint their toenails red?",
    "answer": "So they can hide in cherry trees without being seen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why do ducks have webbed feet?",
    "answer": "So they can stamp out forest fires"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why do elephants have large, flat feet?",
    "answer": "So they can stamp out burning ducks"
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the difference between a prune and an elephant?",
    "answer": "They're both purple except for the elephant"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did George Washington say when he saw the elephants coming over the hill?",
    "answer": "\"Here come the elephants\""
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Charles DeGaul say when he saw the elephants coming over the hill?",
    "answer": "\"Viola, voici les elephants,\" which is French for \"Here come the elephants\""
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Tarzan say when he saw the elephants coming over the hill?",
    "answer": "\" Ahhhhhhh...ahh..ah..ah...ah...ahhhhhhhhh,\" which is Tarzan for \"Here come the elephants\""
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Jane say when she saw the elephants coming over the hill?",
    "answer": "\"Here come the prunes.\" You see, Jane's color blind."
  }
]